Wolf, William B. Additional Papers 6138
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
William B. Wolf Additional Papers
1958-2000
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Wolf, William
6138
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Papers.
5817057
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, October 11, 2001
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 23, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6305: William B. Wolf Papers 6305 AV: William B. Wolf Audio-Visual 6305 P: William B. Wolf Photographs
Wolf, William B.; Academy of Management -- Archives
5817057
- Academy of Management Panel, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Academy of Management, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Scope and Contents
  December 1967 Meeting
- Academy of Management National Roster ND, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Academy of Management, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  December 1966 Meeting
- Academy of Management Membership Drives, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Academy of Management Meeting, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Academy of Management Research Proposal, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Academy of Management National Program, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Articles submitted for Academy of Management Meeting, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Lazarus, Harold-Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Litterer, Joseph-Correspondence, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- McSparrin, Bruce-Correspondence, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Richards, Max, 1966-1968 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Academy of Management-Rosters, 1963-1968 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Academy Meetings-Budget, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Correspondence Submitted Papers, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Committee Meeting Rooms to be Reserved, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- People Requesting Program Notices, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Commitments for the December Program, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Academy of Management Committee on Comparative Administration, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Academy of Management-International Business Workshop, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Academy of Management Program-Predictive Studies, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Academy of Management Newsletters, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Academy of Management-Comparative Management Committee, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Council for Professional Education in Business, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Academy of Management-Constitution and By-Laws, 1958-1969 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Academy of Management-Placement Service, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Academy of Management-Subcommittee on Comparative Management, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Academy of Management-Book Awards, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Academy of Management Meeting, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Academy of Management Meeting-Regional Papers, 1966-1968 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Academy of Management, Western Division Workshop, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Academy of Management-IRRA Meeting, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Academy of Management-Western Division-Committee on Comparative Administration, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Academy of Management-Office of the President, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Academy of Management-Routine Correspondence, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Academy of Management History, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- History Division, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Academy of Management-Nominations for Fellows, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Academy of Management-Meeting, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Academy of Management Newsletter, 1982-1988 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Academy of Management News, 1988-1995 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  incomplete
- Academy of Management News, 1966-1999 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Business Policy and Strategy Newsletter, 1994-1999 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Managerial Consultation Division Newsletter, 1990-1999 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- SIM (Social Issues in Management) Newsletter, 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Human Resources Division News, 1994-1999 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- OB (Organizational Behavior Division of the Academy of Management) News, 1990-1999 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Organization and Management Theory Division Newsletter, 1987-1999 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- The Chronicles, 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Academy of Management Placement Rosters, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Academy of Management Handbook, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Consulting Practice Communique, 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- International Management Newsletter, 1987-1990 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- ODC (Organization Development and Change Divison of the Academy of Management) Newsletter 1992, 1996-1997, 1999-2000 (incomplete), 1992-2000 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Historically Speaking, 1997-1999 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- International Management Division Newsletter, 1994-1999 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Management History Division Newsletter Fall, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Personnel/ Human Resources Division Newsletter, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  Mar-82
- Western Academy of Management Newsletter, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  May-97
- Business Policy and Planning Newsletter, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  Spring 1982
- Academy of Management Fellows, 1989-1998 (Box 1, Folder 62)
- "Some Great Ideas in Public Administration..." Robert Golembiewski, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 63)
- The Academy of Management, 1989-1999 (Box 1, Folder 64)
- Academy of Management Nominees for Membership, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 65)
- Biographical Sketches, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 66)
- ILR Building Dedication Weekend Highlights, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  4/16-18/98
- Academy of Management Related Seminars and Conferences ND, 1968-1998 (Box 1, Folder 68)